[{"answer": "Recognize this", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "that place found it in the extraterrestrial's suit", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Steering wheel", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Gear shift", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Gear shift", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Dashboard", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " What?", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Police..", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Steering wheel... gear shift... dashboard..", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Good", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Pancakes", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " When can we expect containment", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " It's in a green Mustang", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " What?", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " that place... that place..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "No gas... car dead.  We need gas. I don't want to get shot for running out of gas", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Yes. Very good", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Go", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Closed", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "My... husband", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No. I don't know what you are, but you're not my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " I..", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I want to try it", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " When do you have to be here", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " How will I do this one?..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "But I speak English", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " I do not speak English", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Your thumb tells the driver that you want a ride", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Not every car, but... a car will stop... Maybe not the first car... maybe number eight, number fifteen..", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You did? That's funny. So did we", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Yes", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I don't understand 'friend.", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "He was a good friend... The captain took the ship away fast and I was not in the ship", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I'd like to hear it. Can you sing something", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Don't be afraid... I'd really like to hear it", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I'll take that", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Credit card", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Good job, neither do I. What do you do for a living", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I'm a cook. Do you understand 'cook?", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I told you goodbye. Why are you here", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "This car will take me to that place. I cannot go back", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " Hello... hello. How are you this morning", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " No, they don't talk... We talk to them", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "You're not hearing me", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "We'll do that. But how are we going to hold him? He can change himself into a man. He can disappear", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " Many of my people will not believe those things are possible. On my planet there is only one government, one people, one language. I will be asked a lot of questions", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I will say that we can be friends", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Where do you think you're going", "docId": "Starman.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "I said I would get you to your ship and that's where we're going to say goodbye", "qsentId": 50}]